You're famous.
你出名了.
I'm not famous. We are famous.
不是我出名了.是我们出名了.
The office is famous.
我们的办公室出名了.
That's funny.
真奇怪.
I didn't see a picture of the office in the paper.
我没有在报纸上看到办公室的照片.
I saw a picture of you.
但我看到了你的照片.
Is there a picture of me?
有我的照片吗?
Page28.
第28页.
You're famous.
你出名了.
This is terrible.
这太糟糕了.
What's terrible?
什么太糟糕了?
Where did they get this picture?
他们从哪儿弄到这张照片的?
Ah, Richard, it's the price of fame.
Ah, Richard,这就是出名的代价.
Joe. I'm not famous.
Joe.我没出名.
But there are better pictures of me.
可我有比这更好的照片.
An interview here.
这儿登一个采访.
Another picture there.
那儿再登一张照片.
Soon you'll be on television.
很快你就将上电视了.
Excellent. You can go on a talk show.
好极了.你可以上电视访谈节目了.
Then comes the book.
然后会有关于你的书出版.
And the movie.
然后拍成电影.
An adoring public.
还有热爱的公众.
Great parties.
盛大的晚会.
No privacy. A twenty-four-hour-a-day job.
没有隐私.一天24小时工作.
No normal life.
没有正常人的生活.
Details.
都是细节问题.
I don't believe this.
真不敢相信.
Do you really want to be in the public eye?
你真想成为公众瞩目的人物?
I do. I want to go on a talk show.
是的.我想上电视访谈节目.
Joe. You're much more reserved than I am.
Joe. 你比我更内向.
You don't want to be famous.
你不想出名吧.
No. Not me. I'm smarter than that.
对.我不想.我可没那么傻.
I want you to be famous.
我想让你出名.
Yes, Trish?
什么事,Trish?
It's the State Attorney General for you,
是州首席检察官找你，
Mr.Hobart. Line 2.
Hobart先生.2号线.
Thank you.
谢谢.
You're famous.
你出名了.